{
    "target_configs": {
        "player": {
            "name": [
                "player_4_9WWAT8",
                "player_7_9WWAT8",
                "player_10_9WWAT8",
                "player_6_9WWAT8",
                "player_11_9WWAT8"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                4,
                7,
                10,
                6,
                11
            ],
            "animation": [
                "crouch",
                "liedown",
                "stand",
                "crouch",
                "stand"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "A woman with fair skin, wearing a white and blue shirt, blue pants, dark boots, a gray bandana, and a utility belt with pouches",
                "A bald man with glasses, dark complexion, wearing a black turtleneck, suit, and shoes",
                "A man with medium skin, wearing sunglasses, maroon polo shirt, beige pants, brown shoes, and a watch",
                "A female soldier with light skin, wearing a black beanie, tactical vest, black shirt, pants, and boots, with a white scarf and communication gear.",
                "A man with short black hair, wearing a white button-up shirt, dark pants, and black shoes. Light skin tone."
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    16831.071,
                    -82523.433,
                    5577.598,
                    0,
                    -140.60730946073818,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    16853.915,
                    -82427.342,
                    5552.517,
                    0,
                    -157.02817039258167,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    17098.332,
                    -82065.186,
                    5409.836,
                    0,
                    88.70195865057173,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    17263.261,
                    -82582.655,
                    5465.203,
                    0,
                    40.78312091165725,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    17670.459,
                    -82820.611,
                    5506.768,
                    0,
                    53.492180870407736,
                    0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None"
            ]
        },
        "drone": {
            "name": [
                "drone_0_9WWAT8"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                0
            ],
            "animation": [
                "none"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "Aerial drone with a black and white frame, dual rotors, and a streamlined design."
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    16781.608,
                    -82059.557,
                    5739.65,
                    0,
                    64.34544617818273,
                    0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None"
            ]
        }
    },
    "sample_configs": {
        "sample_center": [
            17357.643,
            -82626.018,
            5450.953
        ],
        "sample_radius": 1012.7493731495551
    },
    "refer_agents_category": [
        "player",
        "drone"
    ],
    "safe_start": [
        [
            17219.984,
            -83412.285,
            5529.511,
            0,
            97.8005186723927,
            0
        ],
        [
            17973.82,
            -82048.948,
            5272.342,
            0,
            -157.7619787775227,
            0
        ],
        [
            16533.949,
            -83162.582,
            5655.773,
            0,
            53.767992047396554,
            0
        ]
    ],
    "Questions": {
        "relative_distance": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_floral_shirt, the_bald_man_in_glasses or the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_bald_man_in_glasses",
                    "B. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_bald_man_in_glasses"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_floral_shirt, the_woman_in_black_vest or the_man_in_white_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_black_vest",
                    "B. the_man_in_white_shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_black_vest"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_glasses, the_woman_in_floral_shirt or the_man_in_white_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_floral_shirt",
                    "B. the_man_in_white_shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_glasses, the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants or the_man_in_white_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants",
                    "B. the_man_in_white_shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants, the_bald_man_in_glasses or the_man_in_white_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_bald_man_in_glasses",
                    "B. the_man_in_white_shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_bald_man_in_glasses"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_black_vest, the_bald_man_in_glasses or White_Drone?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_bald_man_in_glasses",
                    "B. White_Drone"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_bald_man_in_glasses"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_white_shirt, the_woman_in_black_vest or the_woman_in_floral_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_black_vest",
                    "B. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_black_vest"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Which is closer to White_Drone, the_bald_man_in_glasses or the_man_in_white_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_bald_man_in_glasses",
                    "B. the_man_in_white_shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_bald_man_in_glasses"
            }
        },
        "counting": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "How many unmanned aerial vehicles are present in the picturesque landscape?",
                "answer": "One"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "How many human figures are positioned in a crouch on the verdant hillside?",
                "answer": "Two"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Among the individuals scattered across the slopes, how many are male?",
                "answer": "Three"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "How many female individuals are currently in the scene?",
                "answer": "Two"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "How many of the people visible are wearing corrective eyewear?",
                "answer": "Two"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "How many of the individuals in the scene have a completely hairless scalp?",
                "answer": "One"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "How many people with a medium skin complexion are also wearing glasses?",
                "answer": "One"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "How many people in the scene are neither bald nor wearing glasses?",
                "answer": "Three"
            }
        },
        "state": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. stand",
                    "B. crouch",
                    "C. sitting",
                    "D. walking"
                ],
                "answer": "B. crouch"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "What's the state of the bald man in glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. liedown",
                    "B. stand",
                    "C. sitting",
                    "D. running"
                ],
                "answer": "A. liedown"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in burgundy polo and light pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. sitting",
                    "B. stand",
                    "C. crouch",
                    "D. jumping"
                ],
                "answer": "B. stand"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. stand",
                    "B. liedown",
                    "C. crouch",
                    "D. sitting"
                ],
                "answer": "C. crouch"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in white shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. crouch",
                    "B. liedown",
                    "C. stand",
                    "D. running"
                ],
                "answer": "C. stand"
            }
        },
        "relative_location": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Where is the bald man in glasses relative to the woman in floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. To the left of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the right of"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Where is the man in burgundy polo and light pants relative to the woman in floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Behind",
                    "B. To the front-right of",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. In front of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the front-right of"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in black vest relative to the woman in floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Behind",
                    "B. To the left of",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. In front of"
                ],
                "answer": "D. In front of"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in floral shirt relative to the man in burgundy polo and light pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-right of",
                    "B. To the back-left of",
                    "C. In front of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the back-left of"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in black vest relative to the man in burgundy polo and light pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the right of",
                    "B. In front of",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the left of"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Where is the man in burgundy polo and light pants relative to the woman in black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the left of",
                    "B. In front of",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the right of"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Where is the man in white shirt relative to the woman in black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Behind",
                    "B. To the front-left of",
                    "C. To the back-right of",
                    "D. In front of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the front-left of"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in floral shirt relative to the man in white shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. To the left of",
                    "C. Behind",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. Behind"
            }
        }
    }
}